[
  [
    {
      "question": "What color was Theseus supposed to change his sails to?",
      "answers": ["black", "white", "red"],
      "correct": 2
    }, 
    {
      "question": "What did Ariadne give Theseus to help him defeat the Minotaur?",
      "answers": ["thread", "food", "a sword"],
      "correct": 1
    }, 
    {
      "question": "What war did Odysseus fight in?",
      "answers": ["World War 2", "The Titanomachy", "The Trojan War"],
      "correct": 3
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is Athena not associated with?",
      "answers": ["wisdom", "warfare", "wilderness"],
      "correct": 3
    }, 
    {
      "question": "How many Olympians are there?",
      "answers": ["36", "3", "12"],
      "correct": 3
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Which gods were the first to emerge after the creation of the cosmos?",
      "answers": ["Olympians", "Titans", "Primordials"],
      "correct": 3
    }, 
    {
      "question": "What is Gaia the personification of?",
      "answers": ["Earth", "sky", "mountains"],
      "correct": 1
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Who did Cronus imprison?",
      "answers": ["Cyclops", "Zeus", "Titans"],
      "correct": 1
    }, 
    {
      "question": "On which island was Rhea worshipped?",
      "answers": ["Ithaca", "Crete", "Mykonos"],
      "correct": 2
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Zeus receives the sky, Poseidon the sea, and Hades the",
      "answers": ["underworld", "land", "air"],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Who wrote the Odyssey?",
      "answer": "homer"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Who was the King of the Titans?",
      "answer": "zeus"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Who was destined to be overthrown by one of his children?",
      "answer": "uranus"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "The Titans were bainshed to the __________",
      "answer": "underworld"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "Who did Pasiphae care for?",
      "answer": "the minotaur"
    }
  ]
]